[Music]
And Rahul and Aditya have joined us.
Rahul ji, first of all, I will
turn to you. Tell me where are you seeing opportunities in terms of trading today?
Hello and good afternoon. So, one long
side trade, one short side trade. The
long side trade will be in PNB. The
stock is trading at its high. It has
crossed the last resistance and is
forming a strong bullish candle. Today, you can go
long at the market price. The stop
loss is 129,
129.99, keep it at 1580. So, one long
trade and one short trade. From my side, okay? So,
here
you are getting a sell advice and a short trade in ICICI Labad.
You can go long in PNB. Let's
move ahead for the target of 144.
Aditya, tell me which
stocks are on your radar. Prashant, good afternoon. I
would like to go with two buy recommendations. The first
stock is Havells. The stock has shown a very strong up move
and I feel that
all these summer stocks are doing very well.
Blue Star, Phatak, Havells, Vega, all are
doing well.  So I think the
rally in Havells will continue and you
can buy at fresh levels from here. Above you
will see a target of 1680. Below there is a stock loss of 1475. A
fresh up move is very good in this.
I feel that a great up move is coming in this.
My second stock recommendation will be here.
If we look at the delivery side, the stock has
now shown a breakout after a very good consolidation
and I feel that the stock will see
a fresh up move coming.
This will be a positional trade because big
targets are coming. The target here will be 500. The
stop loss is placed at 442 and
a fresh entry can be taken in this. The volume build-
up is also very good in the delivery side,
so I feel that a fresh long
addition should definitely be done here.
So these are today's stocks
suggested by our experts in terms of trading. Realty stocks are also
seeing a great rally today. Stocks
like Oye Gadj Properties, Mahindra Life Space are
up today. Ah Rahul, do you think any stock
looks good for you to take entry in Realty?
Actually,
you saw this interesting this morning itself.  I was
observing the chart of DLF. There was a good rally
in DLF. If you notice the weekly candle, there is
a very long week formed
above the high, which is not a good sign at all. So
if you see a closing above 940,
first you can go long in DLF again. The
current market price is hovering around 903,
so you can go long only above 940, otherwise don't go long. The
second
chart I was looking at was of Oye Reality.
Oye Reality also
unfortunately
looks good. You should keep an eye on it.
Apart from this, now we are seeing that
good buying is visible in metal stocks as well. Vedanta is
trading near its 52 week high.
If we talk about the metal space,
Aditya, what would be your advice here? The
stock has been running in Vidanta for quite some time. The
buying seen in metal stocks, there was a
slight correction in between, but it is gaining
momentum again today. These
stocks, Vedanta or any other metal stock, should
definitely be on your radar.  I
feel that the entire metal
segment is witnessing a good momentum build-up
here and this should continue. I
feel that in the coming week too, I feel that we will see
a good momentum build-
up in it. First let us talk about Vedanta. There was a
lot of underperformance. There were
reasons for this, there was a new slowdown due to which the
stock was underperforming. Now
we are seeing an outperformance. Vedanta
stock is already up at 17 this week.
I feel that there is more upside
in the stock. If you want to take a fresh entry, then
if you get a small dip close to
about 310-300 levels, then you can make a fresh addition.
If you already have the stock, then place a
stop loss below 310 and
you can stay put. The first target in the stock will be
345. If it sustains above that, then
we can see the levels of 380.
If we talk about this entire segment,
any other stock which
I am looking good in so far  Momentum has come and it
can come more. I feel that Z
Steel is seeing a good momentum build up here.
I have
an immediate resistance of 895 on the upside, so that will be the
first target of 895 and
we have to place a stop loss of 850 on the downside and if it
crosses 895 then I feel that levels of 3910 can
also be seen here. So
JS Steel is still worth buying at current levels
because we still see that momentum here has
not come that much
buying. Pay out performance can be seen here,
so in terms of right reward and
setup, I feel that Z
Steel will be good for fresh long.
Absolutely, this opinion is
visible in the action coming on these stocks.
One of these stocks is NMDC Steel,
although a slight rise is seen here. There is
pressure in NLC India today and IOC. Among the
oil marketing companies that were running, there is
pressure in IOC today too.
What is your view on IOC, NMDC Steel and NLC India,
Rahul ji  Please give a detailed view on these three stocks. The
first stock, if
I heard correctly, was IOC.
Right, Rahul ji, IOC. Yes, if we
start with IOC first, it has started making lower highs and lower lows
since February 2024. If
you notice the chart, the previous high is
178, the current market price is
167. The previous high is around 178 and it has
not crossed it. It has to make a lower high and
now it is also going to make a lower low. So, we will
not long it in this,
please if you repeat the name of the other counter,
sorry,
NMDC Steel. NMDC Steel. Alright, the
structure in NMDC Steel is a little better because
after a good up move, consolidation is being seen since the last four-five days. In
my
opinion, if someone wants to go long, they
can go long above 6550. The
current market price is 62. One can go long above 6550.
Or if the stock comes down to
around 58, then also one can go long
where there is a buy.  If it is trading at 62 p. It can go
long above 65 5.5 p.m. or if it reaches 58 p.m., you
can go long by keeping a stop loss at 5550 p. MD. There
is another stock NLC India, please give your opinion on that as well.
So, you will notice a similar chart of NLC India, it is
consolidating since last four-five days.
An inverted head and shoulders is currently
forming. The stock has not formed yet, but
its breakout will be known only after 250 p.m. So, right now it is
in the no trade zone. If the inverted head
and shoulders, which is considered a conventional pattern,
breaks out
above 250 p.m., then again we will have to take a call whether we
can go long or
not. So this is the advice, let's look at the NLC India
stock. Aavas Financials
stock is also bullish since this morning. It has now gone up %.
Those who have taken this stock for trading,
Rahul, what should they do? They should exit now after
booking profits and
talk about financials. Correctly right, yes, so
after a continued lower lose and lower high in Aavas Financials, there was
a sudden up today.  A spurt has been seen,
you will notice that two-three days ago also a
big green candle was formed, the stock went up at 10, so at
this point in time a
resistance zone is coming around 1620, so there will
not be any possibility of going long right now, if any one
high is crossed then only you will know whether the stock has ultimate strength
or not, it is called dead cat
bounce in technical terms, then the
first high will be 1620, if it is
sustained above it then only you can
go for a lock with a short to medium term perspective, till then it will be
advisable not to enter this stock,
okay, so this view is on the trap for
you at this time